I'm going to come into the rolling pin to further open up her shoulders and stretch that trapezius muscle.
I'm going to use a pillow here.
I'm going to place it between us.
I'm going to come into the warrior stance and place her arm, the opposite arm that I'll be working on over my leg so she's comfortable.
Tilting your head slightly off the sides.
And then place the arm on the shoulders and then start gently rolling it out, rolling it out, and rolling it out.
Starting from the base of the neck and roll out to before you feel that shoulder bone.
If you've got a real skinny person that has nice little boney shoulder, make sure you never press directly onto that bone.
Keep rolling it out and rolling it out.
Think of a nice rolling pin.
Let the palm be up when you're done.
Start with the palm down, bringing the palm up.
Kind of move position, a little higher and a little lower until you completely relax the shoulder, open up that trapezi muscle, feels really good.